# Examples for Crypto Trading Assistant

Create a plan and a final trading guide using the two-stage prompt chaining.

Example 1: Short-term momentum trade
I want a short-term momentum trade on BTC/USDT. Capital: $1000. Max risk per trade: 2%. Timeframe: intraday (1-4 hours). Prefer using limit orders on Binance.

Example 2: Conservative portfolio rebalancing
I have $10,000 and want a conservative rebalancing plan: 60% BTC, 30% ETH, 10% stablecoins. Low risk, use dollar-cost averaging over 4 weeks.

Example 3: Swing trade with defined stop-loss
Target: ETH/USDT swing trade aiming for 8-12% profit in 1-7 days. Capital: $2000. Max drawdown per trade: 5%. Use a stop-loss and take-profit.

# Example CLI commands:
# python app.py --prompt "I want a short-term momentum trade on BTC/USDT. Capital: $1000, max risk 2%" --temperature 0.7
# python app.py --prompt "Conservative rebalancing to 60% BTC, 30% ETH, 10% stablecoins over 4 weeks" --max_tokens 3000